Biginari Expedition!
Beginner Expedition!
Where to?
This way! The Starlust of the Viginag
It's going to be a biginari talk!
This is Digital Mu!
Pleased to meet you.
We are the Biginari Expedition!
Come on, Captain.
Today...
I boiled my hands a little bit.
Don't make me look like a suspect.
Today is April 21st.
April 21st.
Yesterday, there was an event at Umi-no-Mori Aquarium, and today there is an event at E-Beans.
We're filming an expedition there, and we're at the Garden Terrace in the forest on the 4th floor.
And the penguins from the aquarium are visiting the Garden Terrace on the 4th floor.
The penguins from the aquarium are here to play.
He's almost transformed. Amazing! So, I can't touch them today, but...
But I'd like to introduce you to the penguins.
Let's go to the penguin factory.
Okay, we're here at the penguin factory.
He's in the middle of the 4th floor, right in the bottom where they always have live shows.
It says "Splashmount.
Let's take a look at them. They're really cute. They seem to have a name.
These two penguins.
These two are Bai-chan and the one facing the day after tomorrow is Koa-chan.
Koa-chan? And the one facing the day after that is Koa-chan.
Great! So cute!
Hello. This way.
Oh, they're here.
They're fangirling.
He's so cute.
Hey, Bay.
And there's Koa.
Hohoho hoho.
What's that?
There's a big penguin.
What's with the penguins?
What's this? It's out of the frame.
It's Gonzalez.
Gonzalez?
This is Goloto.
Gonzalez.
Isn't he big? Just one.
What's going on in there?
Gonzalez, Koa and Pei...
They don't get along.
He's nodding.
You know what I mean?
They're out of bounds because they don't get along with me.
That's too bad.
You're a big boy. You don't move.
It's your job, after all.
You seem a little down.
Not well?
Pen, pen, pen... Oh, he talked.
He talked.
Do penguins say "pen"?
When they're sad, they call them penguins.
I see.
I forgot to eat breakfast today.
Ging.
What do you want to do? I don't know...
I don't know... feed him.
Well, I forgot to eat breakfast.
Yeah.
So, what do penguins eat?
What do they eat? They always eat...
Rice pens.
Oh, rice pens.
They eat rice.
Do you like ice cream?
Pen.
Oh, I think she likes ice cream.
Okay, well...
Something cold.
Pen, pen, pen.
Oh, I see. Something cold.
I have some water here.
Yeah, yeah.
There's a new gelato shop on the first floor of e-Bean's.
You know it?
Ging!
Ging! Is it sad? That's it.
Pen!
Oh, you know.
Pen-Pen!
Gonzalez knows it, too.
I think Gonzalez knows it too.
Do you like gelato?
Pen-Pen!
Want some?
Peng!
Want some? Let's go eat.
Let's eat.
Let's go to the gelato shop on the first floor.
Oh, my hand! Hands! Hands!
There it is.
So, do you want to move on? To the gelato shop.
Mr. Fujitani was like a keeper.
Okay. - Okay.
Gonzalez, a moment.
Yes, sir.
Can I ask you to take me downstairs?
Then let's walk.
I'd like to go to the gelato shop.
What flavor?
Matcha?
Wait a minute.
It's already falling apart.
Then I'd like to go to the gelato shop to eat matcha green tea.
Then let's go on foot.
I'm off!
Fast forward!
We've arrived!
We've arrived.
What do we do now?
Always, Karen.
Gonzales.
You like sesame.
I'll order one.
A sesame?
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, please.
What's the most popular so far?
What's the most popular?
Today's most popular is cream cheese.
Cream cheese?
It's next on my must-try list.
Why?
Oh, my God!
That's amazing! It looks rich.
It looks rich.
Wow!
It's too rich.
I had a bite of it as an extra. What flavor do you want?
Cream cheese.
The most popular.
Good for you.
And it's not just one bite.
On the contrary. - Wow.
I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
Well, good day to you.
Today's Bonzalez breakfast.
Isn't that it?
I'll have to feed Miyu.
A spoon?
You don't have hands, do you?
Time to feed her.
One cream cheese.
That's big!
It's not like it's near a vase or anything.
Near a vase?
Okay, I'll go.
Is it good?
Yummy.
Good for you.
It's so good.
It's so good. It's so good.
It's coming out.
Next, a good-luck charm?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
It's so rich!
The sesame is amazing! It tastes amazing because it has a decent amount of sweetness.
You can taste the milk. The root.
It's all very rich, plus if it's sesame, there's a sesame flavor, and the cream cheese is soooo good.
And the aftertaste, it's a little bit delicious.
Maybe there are blueberries in it. You are a very good food reporter.
It's not like it's his first time. Actually, Miyu and I just had it at Gakugei.
I got some milk, and it was really rich. The milk was really rich, really rich, and it was really delicious.
I also recommend Montsales.
Montsalles, too. Oh, my finger.
You can see my finger. I knew it. Maybe it's because he ate the gelato that he's coming in closer to humans.
Maybe.
That's disgusting.
So, today's expedition team visited J-ACO, a gelato shop in Sendai.
It was delicious. It was delicious. Everything was really delicious.
And they have a lot of varieties. I hope you will come again and again to enjoy it. I want to conquer all of them.
The staff were all smiling and full of love.
It's right in front of the specials on the first floor, so I hope everyone enjoys their meal.
That concludes today's expedition. Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
Now, I have to go back to my post at Cornesales.
I'm going to the Sea Forest Aquarium.
Are you okay?
I have to go.
I'm going to buy some stuff earlier.
Thanks.
Yeah. - Okay.
See you later.
Bye.
Bye-bye.
Where were we?